let savollar4 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "appropriate",
        answer: "A. to'g'ri",
        options: [
            "A. to'g'ri",
            "B. qulay",
            "C. katta",
            "D. kichik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "to avoid",
        answer: "B. olib qochmoq",
        options: [
            "A. ketmoq",
            "B. olib qochmoq",
            "C. xohlamoq",
            "D. o'ylanmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "to behave",
        answer: "D. o'zini tutmoq",
        options: [
            "A. baqirmoq",
            "B. yig'lamoq",
            "C. kulmoq",
            "D. o'zini tutmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "calm",
        answer: "C. hotirjam",
        options: [
            "A. shovqinli",
            "B. qizg'in",
            "C. hotirjam",
            "D. xavotirli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "concern",
        answer: "A. tashvish",
        options: [
            "A. tashvish",
            "B. baxt",
            "C. qiziqish",
            "D. orzu"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "content",
        answer: "B. hursand",
        options: [
            "A. g'amgin",
            "B. hursand",
            "C. xafa",
            "D. quvnoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "to expect",
        answer: "C. kutmoq",
        options: [
            "A. unutmoq",
            "B. sevmoq",
            "C. kutmoq",
            "D. yoqtirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "frequently",
        answer: "A. tez-tez",
        options: [
            "A. tez-tez",
            "B. kamdan-kam",
            "C. ba'zan",
            "D. hech qachon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "habit",
        answer: "B. odat",
        options: [
            "A. harakat",
            "B. odat",
            "C. qoida",
            "D. maqsad"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "to instruct",
        answer: "C. o'rgatmoq",
        options: [
            "A. o'rganmoq",
            "B. sinab ko'rmoq",
            "C. o'rgatmoq",
            "D. kuzatmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "issue",
        answer: "A. masala",
        options: [
            "A. masala",
            "B. muvaffaqiyat",
            "C. reja",
            "D. orzu"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "none",
        answer: "D. hech qancha",
        options: [
            "A. hamma",
            "B. ba'zi",
            "C. ko'p",
            "D. hech qancha"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "patient",
        answer: "B. sabrli",
        options: [
            "A. shoshqaloq",
            "B. sabrli",
            "C. jahldor",
            "D. dangasa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "positive",
        answer: "A. ijobiy",
        options: [
            "A. ijobiy",
            "B. salbiy",
            "C. neytral",
            "D. shubhali"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "to punish",
        answer: "C. jazolamoq",
        options: [
            "A. mukofotlamoq",
            "B. yordam bermoq",
            "C. jazolamoq",
            "D. kechirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "to represent",
        answer: "D. vakil bo'lmoq",
        options: [
            "A. yashirmoq",
            "B. unutmoq",
            "C. sotmoq",
            "D. vakil bo'lmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "to shake",
        answer: "B. silkitmoq",
        options: [
            "A. ko'tarmoq",
            "B. silkitmoq",
            "C. tushirmoq",
            "D. ko'rmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "to spread",
        answer: "A. yoymoq",
        options: [
            "A. yoymoq",
            "B. yig'moq",
            "C. to'plamoq",
            "D. yopmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "to stroll",
        answer: "C. sayr qilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. yugurmoq",
            "B. sakramoq",
            "C. sayr qilmoq",
            "D. uxlamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "village",
        answer: "B. qishloq",
        options: [
            "A. shahar",
            "B. qishloq",
            "C. davlat",
            "D. mamlakat"
        ]
    }
];
